<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="rss.css" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

<channel>
<title>Your RSS Feed Title</title>
<description>A brief description of your RSS feed.</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<link>http://yourwebsite.com/rss.xml</link>
<atom:link href="http://yourwebsite.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

<!-- LB -->

<item>
<title>First Post</title>
<guid>https://dylrex.github.io/2021.html#first-post</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 11:42:09 +1100</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[
<h3>An Introduction - 안녕하세요</h3>

For anyone that my come across this blog, I figure that I should probably post a small introduction and explanation. My name is Dylan and I will be dedicating this blog to my progression in learning Korean. This is mostly a personal project and I want a corner of the internet where I can detail my progress. I will be hosting this temporarily on github and then will probably move to my own hosting when I bother to get that set up. 

<h3>Current starting point</h3>
So far, I have completed the first two <a href="https://talktomeinkorean.com">Talk to me in Korean</a> chapters. So far these seem to be excellent grammar resources that are quite normie friendly, however they provide romanised characters for everything which is not ideal so be aware of that.

I have been consuming Korean media for a few years, mostly with subtitles so I'm not entirely sure how helpful that is but I assume my brain is at least used to hearing the language at this point. I've also tried a few other resources like memrise, lingodeer, korean grammar in use and korean made simple but these weren't for me.

Tl;dr I have 3~ years of experience with korean content, mostly english sub. Studied the language on and off for 6 months or so using traditional methods. 

<h3>The plan going forward</h3>
Going forward, I will be studying mainly using an Immersion approach. Specifically I'm talking about the <a href="https://refold.la/">Refold</a> method. This method seems to be an excellent, non-mindnumbing approach to learning a language which involves getting as much target language input as possible by both actively and passively listenting to or watching korean content and trying to immerse yourself as much as possible to your target language. I've seen progress reports of people that followed similar methods to this such as AJATT and the Mass Immersion Approach and It seems to produce great results in a relatively short amount of time. I still have my reservations about this method because in my mind it seems almost 'too good to be true' but I'm willing to dive in head first for a while and see how much progress I make. 
<br>
<br>
<b>My current self-study plan:</b><br>
<li>Immerse with Korean content for at least 2 hours per day, preferably with Korean subtitles. I will mainly be using Netflix, Viki, Vlive, YouTube and Twitch.</li>
<li>Sentence mine at least a few sentences per day and add those as Anki Cards.</li>
<li>Do Anki reps daily.</li>
<li>I am undecided on this one, I did plan on doing 1 TTMIK lesson per day but I'm contemplating dropping it in favour of aquiring grammar.</li>
<br>
Wish me luck, I will post an update relatively soon and may even verbalise my thoughts in a YouTube video at some point.
<br>
]]></description>
</item>






























</channel>
</rss>

